We rub shoulders with each other every day.
We may not know each other...
but we may become good friends some day.
My name is He Qiwu.
I'm a coop and 223 is my number.
Freeze!
At the closest point of our intimacy...
we were just 00. 00 1 cm from each other.
Fifty-seven hours later.
I fell in love with this woman.
Auntie? This is Wu.
Just wanna say hi... Yes, to you, not to May.
Long time no see. How are you?
I'm fine... Yeah, I think.... it's better
to It May cool down a little first.
I'm sure she'll call me later.
No, don't tell her that I called.
You're going to a movie now?
I'II let you go. Is Uncle there?
Uncle? This is Wu.
Just wanna say hi... How's your cough?
What?
You're going to a movie with Auntie?
I won't hold you, then.
Is May's sister there?
No? Send her my regards.
We all develop our own habits.
Mine is waiting here for May too get off from work.
May likes this place because the manager says
she overlooks like Demi Moore.
We 've separated recently.
May said that I had become more and more
unlike Bruce Willis.
Any message for A/C 3688??
"Love you a million years. "
Ming paged? Do you mean May?
Spell it for me. Is it Ming or May?
You're sure you didn't make a mistake?
Don't you know English?
Ming? Did May ask you to page me?
I'm fine. Tell her not to worry.
I'II take good care of myself.
She can call me any time she wants.
We don't need you as a go-between.
You mean she didn't ask you to page me?
So what's this for?
Go jogging?
Have you fallen out of love again?
Why do I have to jog with you?
What? A contest?
You know that jogging is very personal.
How can you possibly let others see you jog?
Go to bed.
We all have our moments with a broken heart.
Every time I've fallen out of love. I'll go jogging.
Jogging helps too evaporate water
from the body...
so that there won 't be any left for tears.
How can I possibly shed tears?
Too May.
I'm the cool guy.
Still fighting with your girlfriend?
It's almost a month!
Get another one.
Why don't you try May? She's cool.
Hello.
She's getting off early tonight.
Go date her.
She fancies you a lot.
No. I've a date tonight. Somme other time.
- Are you sure you want to do it?
- Yes!
Give me your passports.
Next!
Next one!
Hey, you! You! Sit down.
Lady, is this OK?
Get me a bigger one.
- A plain one. No need to be fancy.
- OK.
Hey. put it down!
I said put it down.
Don't touch.
Give them some beer.
Check, please.
Sometimes I'll spend the night at May's.
Too keep her parents from finding out...
I'd sneak. down from the balcony.
I wonder if I'll be able too do this again.
OK!
- How much?
- $2,500000.
Later, OK?
What are you doing? Go!
Come here.
Follow me. Go check it.
Pack this as well.
OK, OK.
Come.
He's not here.
Do you know where he is?
No.
He left this for you.
The date soon the can tells me
that I don't have much time left.
If I don 't find those Indians.
I'd be in deep trouble.
Why the raincoat?
I think it will rain.
Sometime. somehow.
I've started too be very cautious.
Every time I wear a raincoat.
I'll put soon a pair of sunglasses as well.
One never knows when it's going too rain...
or when it'll be sunny.
Any message for A/C 3688??
- Password please.
- Love you a million years.
Nothing for me?
No calls for yo today.
Thanks.
I took. it as a joke
when she said soon April Fool's Day
that we 'd separate.
I decided too let the joke last for a month.
That's because May loves pineapples.
The first of May is also my birthday.
I promised myself that if May doesn't 't change her
mind after I've bought 33 cans of pineapples...
From that day onwards.
I started too buy a can of pineapples
that'd expire soon the first of May every day.
Then. our love will e expire as well.
Sir, this can will expire tomorrow.
Let me change it for you.
This one is fine.
When is the first flight in the morning?
I'd Like to make a reservation.
one.
- Have you seen these people?
- No.
Look carefully. They're with their kids.
No.
- Have you seen these people?
- I don't know anything.
- No.
- And this? No?
- You really don't know?
- I've no idea where he is.
I saw you talking to him!
No...
Where's my daughter? What do you want?
I'II give you an hour.
If I don't hear anything by then....
you'll never see your daughter again.
An ice creamily for her, please.
Daddy, Daddy!
Somme people are willing to give up their children
for money.
He's not one of them.
An hour later, I left.
Police! Freeze!
I haven't busted any crime for six months.
Hands up!
But I run into this wanted man today.
Every time I solve a case.
I'll always want May too be the first too know.
Hello? Hello?
Bruce Willis, I'II kill you!
Any canned pineapples that expire
on the first of May?
Do you know what day is today?
- April 3000.
- Exactly.
You think We'll sell expired goods?
There are still two more hours to go.
No-one will want anything that's expired.
Go get something fresh.
Fresh? What's so good about being fresh?
Do you realize how much effort has been put
into manufacturing a can of pineapples?
You have to grow it, do the harvest, and slice it.
Throwing them away just like that!
- Do you ever think of what these cans will feel?
- Buddy, I only work here.
Who cares about what these cans feel?
Have you ever thought of my feelings?
It's a blood and sweat job for me!
Of course I wish these cans will never expire.
That will save me a lot of work!
You like expired canned food? Here you are.
Take as much as you like. It's on the house.
Somewhere. somehow.
everything comes with an expiry date.
Swordfish will expire.
Meat sauce will e expire.
Even Glad Wrap will e expire.
I wonder if there 's anything in the world
that won 't e expire?
Hey, you want some canned food?
It's expired! Keep it yourself.
You sure?
I finally found my thirtieth can of pineapples
in a store.
As the first of May begins.
I've come too realize something.
Too May.
I'm no different than a can of pineapples...
You don't want this? It's very tasty... No?
Everyone says that dogs are man 's best friends.
Why does mine
refuse too share my sorrow at the moment?
I bet this must be some record.
I ate all thirty cans of pineapple that night.
Fortunately. May is not into garlic...
How I wish too gooout and celebrate!
May must have gone too bed now.
I wonder if the other May is asleep as well.
Why are you back?
I'm thinking of going to a Late-night movie.
May is gone.
Gone?
You think she'll wait for you?
Women can't afford to wait.
The more they wait, the more they'll get nervous.
Once they're nervous, they'll go nuts.
She went out with Richard.
You'll better be early next time.
It's hard too imagine that I've been dumped
by two Mays soon a single night.
Too heal my wounds.
I've decided too never go out
with another girl called May.
Lulu? This is Wu!
Wanna come out for a drink?
Are you in bed already?
How can you sleep this early?
You can really sleep?
Nothing. Bye.
Hi, Chieko-san? Guess who I am? It's Wu.
Bingo. You're right.
Wanna go out for a drink?
Your husband? When did you get married?
Five years already?
We haven't seen each other
for more than five years?
You have two kids already?
You happy? Great!
OK, keep it up.
Is Jiang Xkiuhuei there?
This is He Qiwu.
I sat next to you in Grade Four.
Don't you remember?
Never mind. Goodbye.
All those pineapples made me feel terrible
in the stomach.
So I go too a bar
thinking that the alcohol will help my digestion.
Are you OK?
Yes, yes. Another double whiskey.
There 's a song called
Love Ends As The Sun Rises.
That's e exactly how I'm feeling.
How can I forget May?
I promise myself.
I'll fall in love with the first woman.
.. who walks into the bar.
Miss, what do you want?
Whiskey, please.
I have a feeling that she 'll like me.
Too make sure of that. I ask. her a question.
Excuse me, miss. Do you like pineapples?
Bet she 's not a native speaker.
Do you like pineapples?
May I know if you like pineapples?
You speak proper Mandarin.
I grew up in Taiwan. And you?
I'm not in a talking mood tonight.
Leave me alone.
We need not speak
May I just sit next to you?
There are lots of seats here.
Why must you sit next to me?
Because I can feel that you're Lonely.
oh, yeah?
Yes.
There are only three reasons for a woman
to wear sunglasses at this hour.
She's either blind,
or she's a pretender,
or she's fallen out of love and doesn't want
people to know she's been crying.
Which type do I belong to?
The broken-hearted.
It's no big deal. You don't have to cry.
I've fallen out of love too.
I would go jogging and sweat it out
so there will be no more water left for tears.
Wanna go jogging?
I've been running for the whole evening
and I'm exhausted.
If you want somebody to talk to,
go find someone else.
I don't particularly want to talk.
Just wanna keep you company.
I know too well what a broken heart feels Like.
At her saddest moment, a woman
will need a man's shoulder to lean on to.
You may take me as your man.
I don't have a man.
I don't have a woman either.
How old are you?
I was 24 two hours ago.
Now I'm 25.
I won't like you.
Don't jump to conclusions.
We may get along with each other.
Do you like pineapples?
That's none of your business.
I'm just trying to Earn more about you.
I was in love with a girl for five years
and we've just separated.
She said I didn't understand her.
That's why I want to find out more about you.
You won't know me.
You won't give me a chance.
OK, you may try to know me.
What kind of men do you like?
Knowing a person doesn't 't mean
you 'll be able too win his love.
A person changes.
He may like pineapples today.
Tomorrow's. he 'll like something else.
Sir...
..we're closing.
closing?
Wanna go jogging?
I just want a place to rest.
I never thought she really meant rest
when she said rest.
I watched two old movies soon TV that night
and had four chef's salads.
As the sunrises, I know it's time for me to go
Before I leave. I take off her shoes for her.
My smoother said
that women will get swollen feet...
.. from sleeping with their high heel shoes soon.
She must have walked a loot last night.
A pretty woman like her
should always have clean shoes.
I was born at 6: 0000am.
Two more minutes and I'll be 25.
In other words. I've lived a quarter of a century.
Too celebrate this historical moment.
I go jogging
too get rid of the e excessive water in my body.
This makes me feel very happy.
When I leave the ball court.
I decide too leave my pager behind...
.. because I know very well
that no-one is going too call me today.
Messages for A/C 3688.
Password. please.
"Love you a million years. "
Your friend in Room 7002 says Happy Birthday.
On May 1. 1 994.
a woman said Happy Birthday too me.
Because of this. I'll remember her all my life.
If memory can be canned.
I hope it will never e expire.
If an e expiry's date must be added onto it.
I hope it will be "a million years".
Give me a cigarette.
It's raining.
oh, yeah?
A Coke, please.
Went jogging again?
A man like you can't jog all day.
Try Faye. She's a good girl.
Who's Faye?
Here's a tip for you. She just came today.
Act fast! Don't let Richard get there before you.
- Thanks a lot. I don't Like men.
- Men?
Excuse me, excuse me.
At the closest point of our intimacy.
we were just 1 cm apart from each other.
I knew nothing about her.
6 hours later.
she fell in love with a man....
A chef salad, please.
For here or
for go?
For go.
Are you new? Never seen you before.
You like loud music??
Yes, the louder the better.
Then I don't have to think.
So you don't like to think?
What do you like?
Never thought about that.
I'II tell you when I've found out myself.
How about you? What do you like?
Chef salad.
Chief, a chef salad, please.
Chef salad again?
Don't you ever get fed up with that?
It's for someone else.
Your girlfriend?
So she really Likes chef salad?
Maybe she's just used to it.
Never said she didn't like it.
Maybe she'll like to try something different.
Try fish and chips. It's good.
What if she doesn't like it?
Buy both and let her choose.
Then you can't go wrong.
Won't that be a waste?
Doesn't cost you much.
It's always good to have a choice.
AII right. one chef salad and one fish and chips.
Good....
Thanks.
Chief, one fish and chips, please.
See? I told you she'd like it.
Well, she should have told me
that she didn't like chef salad.
But you didn't give her any choice.
She'd have told you if she was given a choice.
Talking about a change of taste,
what about trying pizza tonight?
I'm not sure if she'd Like it.
Simple.
Use the same trick: buy them both.
Doesn't cost you much.
- AII right.
- OK.
Hi there. Wanna try something different tonight?
How about a hot dog?
No, thanks, just a cup of black coffee will do.
- Your girlfriend doesn't want anything tonight?
- She has left me.
Why?
She said she wanted to try something different.
Well, I guess she's right. There are just as many
choices with men as with food.
Maybe I should have stuck with chef salad.
No big deal.
How will she know you are the best
if she doesn't try something else?
She'll come back sooner or later. Relax
Thank you.
On board every flight.
there 's always an air hostess
whom you 'll like too seduce.
This time last year. at 25. 000000ft above sea level.
I successfully seduced one.
Do you want a drink?
I thought we 're going too stay together
for a long time...
flying all the way like a plane with a full tank..
I never e expected that it'll change course.
back coffee, please.
It's almost a week now. Has she come back?
Excuse me.
Well, maybe she really has a lot of choices.
Then get her out of your mind.
If she can have her choice.
..why can't you try something different too?
You can't go on drinking black coffee like that.
You don't just change like that.
Let's do that slowly.
I'm all right. Don't worry.
If you say so.
Excuse me,
is there a policeman who comes here
every night for a chef salad?
oh, you mean #633? He's off duty tonight.
I thought he's off on Saturdays.
He's changed shift. Didn't he tell you?
Can you give this to him when you see him?
No problem.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
I've to go out for a while.
- What?
- I've to go out for a while.
OKR....
We have to go out for a while.
What?
- We are taking off for a while.
- Where?
Where are you goin?
-I'll be around...
Huh, how come you're alone tonight?
Huh?
Just you here tonight?
Everyone was here a minute ago
but they all rushed out
when they saw you coming.
Something wrong with me?
Nothing.
back coffee?
Thanks.
Last night...
There's a girl...
What?
I said there's a girl...
Can you turn down the volume?
A girl was here for you Last night.
She left a letter for you.
really?
Yeah... a flight attendant
- Don't you want to have a look?
- I'II finish my coffee first.
Hey, your letter.
Keep it for me. I'II get it some other time.
Chief.
How come it's you?
of course it's me.
Where's #633?
He's having his annual leave.
Annual leave?
Said he hurt himself with a pin.
He's staying home.
Injured by a pin?
Ever since she's left. everything in the house
has become very sad.
Every night. I'll have too woo them too bed.
Do you realize that you've lost a lot of weight?
You used to be cute and chubby.
Now you're so slim.
Why, you must have confidence in yourself.
I told you not to cry. When will you stop crying?
one must be brave.
Look at you. You're so shabby.
Can't even stand up.
Let me help you.
Feel better now?
Say something.
Don't be mad with her.
We all have our moment of doubt.
Give her a chance, OK?
Feeling Lonely?
Just a few days, now look how trashed you are.
Feeling cold?
Let me give you some warm.
Hi there.
Yes, I have. I have it all packed.
- Need some help?
- No, thanks. I can manage.
Excuse me, excuse me.
It's you. How come you're here?
Are you better now?
What do you mean?
They said you were injuried by a pin.
Don't Listen to their shits.
Where're you been lately?
- I changed shift.  This is my juridition now.
- really?
Need some help?
great.
I'm leaving now.
This is heavy!
It's not that heavy today.
This is hard work. for you.
All jobs are like that.
Why did you take this job?
The chief is my cousin.
He couldn't find anyone so he asked
for my help.
What're you done before?
oh, lots of things.
I wanna save some money.
To study?
No. Never thought of that.
I just wanna enjoy life.
How? Where?
Anywhere...
California maybe.
Why California?
I said maybe. If it's no fun,
I can always go some place else.
You like to travel?
Don't you?
I'm very easy-going.
I don't mind staying at one place.
Let's go together.
I've almost saved enough money.
We'll see.
Why are you always like that?
The letter. is still with me.
I haven't got the time to pick it up.
Give me your address and I'II mail it to you.
Then it won't be lost.
OK....
...You're living in the neighborhood.
Yeah, just down the road.
Come and visit me sometime.
Sure, that'll be great.
Well, let's go.
You're sweating. Can you manage?
I'm fine.
Stop day dreaming, will you?
You think you're a superstar?
What are you doing with that carrot?
Who's going to eat that?
You want to sing? Use a toilet roll.
You too.
I'm not day dreaming.
You're right. You're not day dreaming.
You're sleep walking.
Sure... sleep walking
Whatever you say. sleepwalking.
I had a dream that afternoon.
I seemed too have been in his house.
I thought I was going to wake up
when I left the house.
But I just realized that for some dreams.
you simply never wake up.
Sometimes I'll go home for lunch.
because returning home each time
offers another hope.
I know you're in there.
Come out now.
I'II count to three.
One...two...three.
She used too love too dive out from the closet
too scare me.
She doesn't 't do it any more. I know.
you can 't repeat the same game too. often.
Can she be hiding in the washroom?
Hello...
Hello!
Stupid.
Sir, your roasted pork with rice.
Thanks.
Excuse me... excuse me.
It's you again.
That's right.
Will you be here for a while?
Why?
Nothing, nothing.
Hey, where are you heading?
I'm going back for something I've forgotten.
oh, yes, I still haven't mailed your letter.
No hurry.
You sure?
Then I'II send it later when I have time.
Hey, why are you back?
I'm in a hurry to pay the electricity's bill.
Can you look after this for me?
Cousin? I'm still at the marketplace.
What? You're still at the market?
It's pouring here.
Can you hear?
What are you talking about? It's shining here.
really? Must be an isolated shower.
I'II be back as soon as the rain stops.
Don't forget the electricity's bill.
Sure.
I'm going.
OK, I know. I'II come and visit you soon.
I will. Bye-bye.
This is for you.
Why so many lychee's?
They're for a friend.
Where are you?
I'm paying the electricity bill.
You're gone for hours.
There are a lot of people here.
I can't even squeeze in.
Guess I'II just have to wait.
It's impossible. How come it's always crowded?
How do I know?
I'II try my best.
Shall I come again tomorrow?
If it's that crowded, try someplace else.
Someplace else?
OK, I'II try, then. I'm really gonna try now.
Hello...
Hi. You've been shopping?
No, it's for a friend. He's renovating his house.
You sure are busy.
Yes. Surely I am.
back coffee again? It's bad for your health.
Water is what you should have
if you can't sleep at night.
Hi. it's me.
I'm back to Hong Kong.
Want me to reserve a seat for you?
call me. It's the same number. Bye.
What beautiful hair!
How long have you grown it?
It's none of your business. Crazy woman.
Isn't she a bitch?
Yeah.
What?
Nothing...
Well, actually, do you know her very well?
Not really.
One day. I suddenly had this feeling
that she had returned.
I am not sure
if I've forgotten to turn off the tap
or if the house's been getting
more and more sentimental.
I've always thought that it's been
the strongest.
It's been crying a lot.
When a person cries,
you can simply give him a piece of tissue paper
to dry his tears.
But when a house cries,
you really got a lot of hard works to do.
Wow! How come you're here?
- This is my home. of course I'm here.
- Your home?
What are you doing here?
I come to buy goldfish.
- No-one sells goldfish here.
- No?
- You said you came here to buy goldfish?
- Yes.
Do you come here to buy or sell goldfish?
What are you trying to say?
Don't push me.
I can't remember a thing when I'm scared.
Why are you scared?
I don't know! I'm just scared of you.
I'm going now.
What is this? You're still standing here.
Don't rush me!
There's something wrong with my legs.
Are you having a cramp?
How do I know? I've never had one before.
Come in and take a rest.
Every time she returned from a trip.
I'll massage her legs.
Being an air hostess is no easy job.
I always think. that women 's legs are very sexy.
I haven 't touched one since she left.
Feeling better?
Yes. Can I go now?
Stay for a while.
I'II play some music for you.
Do you like this song?
I don't care much for music.
It's my girlfriend's choice.
You sure she liked this song?
Yes.
I know his girlfriend doesn't like this song at all.
The CD was mine. I left it here a few days ago.
I was starting to wonder if sleepwalking
could infect to other people.
Wonder if I've been too nervous.
After a while I just felt asleep
The girl fell asleep in my house that afternoon.
I wanted to wake her up.
but for some reason I didn't do that...
Shit!
Watch out with the fire.
Watch out! Handle the candles with care.
It's all your fault. What's wrong with you lately?
Why didn't you pay the electricity's bill?
Where have you been every day?
To see the doctor.
Doctor? I don't see you talking any medicine.
of course I did. You just didn't notice.
really? Did the doctor tell you
when you'll recover?
It won't take long.
Idiot !
I wonder if it's the weather or what.
Lately. I've found that I've changed a lot.
I've become more observant.
I start too notice a loot of things
which I never paid attention.
Even sardines are tasting differently.
My mother was very pretty in her youth.
You mustn't give yourself up.
How can you have grown so fat
in such a short time?
Even if she's gone,
you still have to carry on with yourself.
You mustn't indulge yourself any more.
Control your diet.
Do you know how you've disappointed me?
You've changed so much.
one mustn't change one's personality.
You mustn't change yourself,
even if she's not coming. back any more.
You really have to reflect on this.
When I see it cry. I actually feel relieved.
Despite the change of its look.
it still remains true too itself.
It is still an emotionally-charged time.
Haven't you noticed
that I've become more optimistic??
I've found that many things are looking better.
You, for example, were a little dumb.
You mustn't make yourself so dirty though.
You used to be so much cleaner.
And look at these yellowish stripes.
Have you been fighting with others?
But you look a lot more cute now.
Why are you hiding here?
I've been looking all over for you.
It's useless lying here.
have to accept reality.
You're starting to smell too.
Let's go sunbathing tomorrow.
What are you doing in my house?
You asked me to visit you sometime.
Open up.
hurry!
Someone's looking for you.
- Me?
- That's right.
Wow!
Why are you here?
I've come for my letter.
What letter.? Ask the chief
You've been keeping it.
- He says it's with you.
- Me? Where?
really?
oh, yes.
I'm just afraid that it'll be lost.
I swear I haven't read it.
Thanks.
Will you be free tomorrow evening?
Why? What do you want?
I want to take you for a date.
- Why do you want to date me?
- The manager said you'll be off tomorrow.
Why should I need a date for a day off?
You think about it.
I'II wait for you at the California Restaurant
tomorrow night at 88.
This song doesn't suit you.
Listen to this.
Shit !
Oh shit !
Didn't know #633 was so good with girls.
- It's #633, Chief!
- Get out of here...
hold... hold on a second. I haven't got...
Chili sauce. Here, here. OK?
Coke, please.
What?
Coke.. the paper cup ran out...
- Mutton.
- Mutton? Ha!
I cleaned up the house that afternoon.
It's like clearing up the runway
for the next flight.
I arrived at the California a little earlier
that evening.
Since I didn 't know how long the flight
will be delayed.
I decided too get some loose change.
Somme loose change, please.
Half an hour later.
I got some more loose change.
I had a feeling that the flight might have been
canceled.
She won't be coming.
She asked me to give you this letter.
No need to be sad though.
Try another one.
May is a good girl. She'll be coming. back to work
tomorrow. Try her.
Where is she?
She's quit. She said she's going to California.
That's all.
Thanks.
I didn't open the letter.
There are things that you need time too accept.
After the manager left.
I started talking too the beer bottles.
Disappointed?
Not really.
Go home and sleep. She 's not coming.
She did indeed go too California that evening.
It's just that it's the other California.
That same evening.
we were at two different California's.
separated by a time difference of 1 5 hours.
It should be 1 1 am now in California. USA.
I wonder if she will remember
that I have a date with her at 8pm.
What a coincidence!
You're off tonight?
Yes.
How are you?
Still the same. And you?
Not bad.
You alone?
I'm with a friend.
Good match.
You still have some stuff at my place.
When will you pick them up?
Don't want them any more. Throw them away.
OK
Got to go now.
- I still think you look better in your uniform.
- You too.
- Bye.
- You haven't paid.
- You pay for me.
How much, please?
The letter turned out to be a boarding pass.
The date. however. was a year later.
I missed the destination
it was blur.
I did go to the restaurant that night.
I knew it would be crowded by 8.
So I arrived at 7: 1 5.
It was pouring that evening.
Thorough the window. I saw a raining California.
I wanted too know desperately if the other
California is warm and sunny.
I decided to give myself one year's time.
Today. the rain is just as heavy as that day.
Looking out of the window.
I only have one person in mind.
I wonder if he had ever opened the letter.
Why are you here?
- Why are you here?
- How come it's you?
What are you doing here?
Refurbishing.
Refurbishing ?
Where's my cousin?
He's opened a karaoke.
He said he wanted a change.
and let me take over.
Didn't he tell you?
I haven't seen him.
He's really got a business sense.
First he sold me the fish and chips,
and then the whole shop.
What?
I said he's got a great business mind.
Since when are you into this kind of loud music??
It takes a little time to get used to
and then it's fine.
Did you go to California?
- Was it fun?
- What?
Did you go to California? Was it fun?
California? Just the same. No big deal.
You look pretty good in uniform.
You look nice in this too.
Want to eat something?
Guess not.
I have an early flight tomorrow.
When will you be back?
I'm opening this in two days' time.
I don't know. This time it may take a while.
Well, write me a letter.
when you reach someplace.
You may not even read it.
Just want to ask you something.
Will you let a person board
with a boarding pass like this?
The date is today,
but the rain blurred it.
I don't know where it's going to. Do you know?
I've no idea.
Let me give you another one.
Great.
Where do you want to go?
Wherever you want to take me to...
Written and directed by
Wong Kar-Wai
Leading players
Brigitte Lin
Tony Leung
Faye Wong
Kaneshiro Takeshi
Guest appearancce - Valerie Chow